http://www.thecolorsofindia.com/privacy.html

Submit Query
About UsAdd to FavoritesContact Us
Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy describes how SAVION TRAVEL SERVICES PVT. LTD. manage personal information and respect your privacy. This policy may be amended from time to time.
1.	Collection of Personal Information: As a visitor to the Site, you can engage in many activities without providing any Personal Information. Depending upon the activity, some of the information that we ask you to provide is identified as mandatory and some as voluntary. If you do not provide the mandatory data with respect to a particular activity, you will not be able to engage in that activity. However, when you register to use SAVION TRAVEL SERVICES PVT. LTD. and order products as a SAVION TRAVEL SERVICES PVT. LTD. customer, in order to provide the services to you, we may collect your contact information such as your name, phone numbers, address and email address as well as profile information, including your password, details about your purchases and details about your interactions with us.
2.	Updating your Personal Information: You have the right to access and correct, or delete your Personal Information and privacy preferences at any time. For security purposes, this may be accomplished by changed by contacting support. We will respond to your request promptly within a reasonable time.
3.	How your Personal Information is used: SAVION TRAVEL SERVICES PVT. LTD. collects your information in order to provide services to you, comply with our legal obligations, and to improve our products and services. We do not sell, rent or share your personally identifiable information to or with third parties in any way other than as disclosed in this Privacy Policy. SAVION TRAVEL SERVICES PVT. LTD. may use this information to -
Process your financial transactions; Service your order.
Respond to customer service requests, questions and concerns.
Administer your account.
Send you requested product or service information.
Keep you informed about special offers and services of SAVION TRAVEL SERVICES PVT. LTD. and selected third parties.
Administer promotions and notify you of important events.
Investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities and/or violations of our Terms of Service.
Meet our research and product/service development needs and to improve our Site, services and offerings.
Customize your experience, including targeting our services and offerings to you.
In certain situations, SAVION TRAVEL SERVICES PVT. LTD. may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities. Where required by law (like to comply with a warrant, court order, or legal notice served on SAVION TRAVEL SERVICES PVT. LTD.), and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, avoid litigation, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, and/or respond to a government request. We may also disclose information about you if we determine that such disclosure should be made for reasons of national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance.
4.	Information sharing with service providers: SAVION TRAVEL SERVICES PVT. LTD. uses one or more outside payment processing companies to bill you for our goods and services. To the best of our knowledge, these companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any other purpose. We also share Personal Information with certain companies that perform services on our behalf. We only share the Personal Information which is necessary for them to perform those services. We require any company with which we may share Personal Information to protect that data in a manner consistent with this policy and to limit the use of such Personal Information to the performance of services for SAVION TRAVEL SERVICES PVT. LTD.. We do not sell or otherwise provide Personal Information to other companies for the marketing of their own products or services.
5.	Data Retention: We will retain your information for as long as your account is active, your information is needed to provide you services, or as required to fulfill our legal obligations. If you wish to delete your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at support@saviontravel.com. We will respond to your request within reasonable time. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements.
6.	Protection of your Personal Information: The Personal Information that you provide in connection with the use of the Site is protected in several ways. It resides on secure servers that only selected SAVION TRAVEL SERVICES PVT. LTD. personnel have access to via password. Your Personal Information is encrypted whenever it is transmitted to SAVION TRAVEL SERVICES PVT. LTD.. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using transport layer security technology. We strive to protect the Personal Information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we take into account the sensitivity of the Personal Information we collect, process and store, and the current state of technology to use these measures protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions, doubts or confusion in regard to any of the terms set out here in the privacy policy, please seek clarifications from us through email (support@saviontravel.com). We will get back to you within reasonable time.
Facts About India
Adventure |
Business |
Culture |
Cinema |
Defence |
Geography |
Government |
